Hey, welcome to this video here from Bavaria. I am in the warehouse of paradise
with Julia and Stephanie Bessler, the founders of paradise. Hi! Hi! Nice to see you!
We had a shooting in the morning already for the new collection. You can see more
of that at the end of the video because now you're going to show me your
warehouse. I'm making all the noise here. Anyway. First, do you want to tell me a few sentences about your brand
Paradise? You found it, I think five years ago. How did that start? We started with bikinis, like reversible
bikinis, perfect for sisters or twins. Best friends, mother and daughter. We had the idea to make leather pants or fake
leather pants. We always like to wear leather items but we couldn't find the
perfect pants for us so we combined special features we liked and created our own.
Obviously we like to pair our Paradise pants with leather jackets and tops.
I also love to pair them with your bodysuits. I think it's also a great match.
What is one of your other favorite styling options? What do you like to style
I think we prefer black.
Oh, I feel that.
Yeah, you can combine black with other colors, different patterns.
So black is always a good idea.
We like crop tops.
So black pants and a red crop top or a white crop top and a blazer is always a good idea.
What was the wildest styling you did with them?
I think two years ago we created a Halloween look and we created an alien costume with lime green ultra pants.
And we had an alien head on our head.
Yeah, an alien mask.
So you basically like to do costumes with them and wear them in everyday life.
So like every day, every occasion.
That's so nice.
I mean, it's perfect that you love to wear your own products.
the best advertising basically. We always wear them everyday. Like not the leather pants but the sport leggings or the shorts in summer.
I feel that I do too.
What is the craziest color you have here?
I think it was a neon orange and neon green but these are already sold out.
So I think we have the neon pink.
Yes.
Neon pink.
Neon pink and different colored leopard pants.
We also have the snake rainbow.
Okay, so it's a lot of different styles.
If someone does not have any Paradise product yet,
what would you recommend as a first item?
I think the classic or ultra pants.
Classic or ultra pants.
So you're wearing the ultra pants.
And we're wearing the classic pants.
They're also available without zipper.
I think we both or we three preferred with zipper.
How many products do you currently have?
I think we have almost 100 different aesthetic pants
or aesthetic leggings, sports bras, sport leggings.
Yeah, something like 100.
Wow.
All right, what's new?
What's next for Paradise, new products?
The next collection will be a sportswear collection.
A combination of leather and sportswear fabric.
And you can see it has a reflective line.
So it's safe when you go out for a run in the night.
So it's activewear fabric and faux leather.
Yes.
Oh, that's cool.
I remember the last time I saw you was in Vienna when we shot the Celine Lox limited
edition.
and it was amazing you told me how to do the po-posing, the booty posing.
It's in German, it's po-posing.
Can you tell and show me again because I didn't, I couldn't do it like that anymore.
So please, you have to put one foot behind the other.
but how far? Like once one big step. One big step. Yes and now focus on this leg and put your weight
on this leg. Yes. And now squeeze your butt and yeah. But where does the camera have to be then
because I think it's also it's also the angle. Yeah. Like it's the same height as the hip. A little bit
from the back and a little bit from back and the hip height or yeah higher lower better too low
than too high better too low yeah and then a lot of booty training yeah i know just just butt squeezing
i don't know
i feel like i'm not pretty stable
It looks good!
Yeah?
I don't know. I don't see it anymore so I have to check the video later.
Thanks for taking the time to show me not only the warehouse but how to pose.
And this nice shooting in the morning although it was very cold.
But we're warm again after some pizza and pasta.
Okay, thanks guys for having me.
You're welcome.
And I hope to see you again soon.
Bye!
You were standing there alone
Looking in
You were a heart with no home
Falling in
Cover up your shoulders
From the rain
Oh, it's pouring
You must be cold
I'm feeling like I'm slipping
It's deep within my soul
It's finding all the answers
The questions I've known
It's common interaction
It's so unlike a scene
I've used my intuition
To find another key
I'm falling in too deep
I am running out of time
I'm using up my oxygen
Wishing you were my